Guide to the Eugene B. Dynkin papers, 1950-2014.
Dynkin, Eugene B. papers,
- Series IX. Audio/Visual material
  - Subseries IXb.Videos
    - Ido, mittag-bettler, Undated; v-10984 (Box 35)
    - Rosh hashana, Undated; v-10985 (Box 35)
    - Home Party, 1999-12-31; v-10986 (Box 35)
    - Moscow, 1962-1975; f-2152 (Box 34)
      Film
    - Tashkent, 1962; f-2153 (Box 34)
    - Vilvnius-Nida, 1964; f-2154 (Box 34)
    - Novosibirsk, Tbilisi, 1963; f-2155 (Box 34)
    - Family USSR, Undated; f-2156 (Box 34)
    - Yug, 1962; f-2157 (Box 34)
    - Adramyevo and more, 1972-1973; f-2158 (Box 34)
    - Bielefeld, Israel Country Club, 1983; f-2159 (Box 34)
    - [Illegible title], 1969; f-2160 (Box 34)
  - Subseries IXc. CDs and DVDs
    - A. Minchenko, Date Unknown; CD-4619
    - Research, 2002; CD-4620
    - Book 2, Date Unknown; CD-4621
    - Book 1, Date Unknown; CD-4622
    - Research backup, Date Unknown; CD-4623
    - Research: selecta 140, 145-171, Date Unknown; CD-4624
    - Research 2B: 171-172, 175, 176, 179-183, Date Unknown; CD-4625
    - Research: 171, 172, 174, 175-183, Date Unknown; CD-4626
    - Untitled, Date Unknown; CD-4627
    - Research 2A, Date Unknown; CD-4628
    - T3 Reflex, Date Unknown; CD-4629
    - Quicken, Date Unknown; CD-4630
    - T3, Date Unknown; CD-4631
    - T3, Date Unknown; CD-4632
    - Demekie 2, Date Unknown; CD-4633
    - A.H. Kolmozoroba, Date Unknown; CD-4634
    - Pictures, 2005-09; CD-4635
    - Baby pictures, 2009-04; CD-4636
    - Slideshow, 2004; CD-4637
    - Untitled, 2004-05-09-2004-05-14; CD-4638
    - Dynkin photos, 1994-2003; CD-4639
    - Italy, 1994-2001; CD-4640
    - Photo, Date Unknown; CD-4641
    - Dina and Or wedding CD 1, Date Unknown; CD-4642
    - Dina and Or wedding CD 2, Date Unknown; CD-4643
    - Dina and Or, 2005-10; CD-4644
    - Karpelevich, Date Unknown; CD-4645
    - Karpelevich's debut, Date Unknown; CD-4646
    - Karpelevich school circle, first course, fourth course, student song, Date Unknown; CD-4647
    - Karpelevich, Date Unknown; CD-4648
    - Video 1, Date Unknown; CD-4649
    - Video 2, Date Unknown; CD-4650
    - House of Fools, Date Unknown; CD-4651
    - EBD memories, Date Unknown; DVD-2684
    - Dynkin (title in russian), 2013; DVD-2685
    - Gorodnitsky, Date Unknown; DVD-2686
    - Dynkin, Kuznetsov, Skorokhod, Date Unknown; DVD-2687
    - Kids, Ido and Yael, 2004-09-13; DVD-2688
    - Karpelevich, Date Unknown; DVD-2689
    - Khasminskii, Freidlin, Wentzell, Krylov, Date Unknown; DVD-2690
    - Dynkin 80 conference and dinner, 2004-05; DVD-2691
    - Malytov, Date Unknown; DVD-2692
    - Marcus, Vanderbei, Ido, Yael, Date Unknown; DVD-2693
    - EBD early life, Date Unknown; DVD-2694
    - Dynkin Interview, 2013-04-08; DVD-2695
    - EBD memories, Date Unknown; DVD-2696
    - LIE days, 2006; DVD-2697-2699
    - 80th Birthday dinner, 2004-05; DVD-2700
    - IGD, EBD, Date Unknown; DVD-2701
    - Dynkin Interview, 2013-04-08; DVD-2702
    - Messiah DVD, Date Unknown; DVD-2703
    - Title illegible, Date Unknown; DVD-2704
    - Markov processes theory, Date Unknown; DVD-2705
    - Title illegible, Date Unknown; DVD-2706
    - Untitled, Date Unknown; DVD-2707
    - Untitled, Date Unknown; DVD-2708
    - 80th conference, 2004-05; DVD-2709
    - Martin Boundary, Date Unknown; DVD-2710
    - Untitled, Date Unknown; DVD-2711
    - Oblique derivative, Date Unknown; DVD-2712
    - Aldous 1, Date Unknown; DVD-2713
    - Markov processes theory, Date Unknown; DVD-2714
    - Berest Alex, Date Unknown; DVD-2715
    - Berest Alex, Date Unknown; DVD-2716
    - Aldous 2, Date Unknown; DVD-2717
    - Minchenko, Date Unknown; DVD-2718
  - Subseries IXd. Photographs
    - Photo album, 1947-1951 (Box 32)
    - Photo album, 1952-1958 (Box 31)
    - Photo album, 1958-1969 (Box 31)
    - Photo album, 1969-1984 (Box 31)
    - Photo album, 1890-1947 (Box 31)
    - Photo album, 1977-1987 (Box 32)
      Includes Japan, Colorado, Baton Rouge, Moscow, Ithaca, China.
    - Photo album, 1987-1993 (Box 32)
      Includes Israel, Ithaca, Singapore, Russia, Edinburgh, Germany, Canada, Tennessee.
    - Photo album, 1993-1995 (Box 32)
      Includes Ithaca, Beijing, Taiwan, Moscow, Minnesota, Sweden
    - Photo album, 1993-1997 (Box 32)
      Includes Stockholm, Ithaca, Paris
    - China photo album, 1958 (Box 32)
    - Photographs of Dynkins and others, Undated (Box 33, Folder 1-2)
    - Copies of photographs, Undated (Box 33, Folder 3-4)
    - Photo album, 1959-2003 (Box 36)
      Includes Olya, Dynkins, various locations and conferences
    - Photo album, 1993-1999 (Box 36)
      Includes various locations and events
  - Subseries IXe. Slides
    - Slide lists for box 12, Undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Slides, 1962-1975 (Box 12)
    - Math 1, 1963-1970 (Box 12)
    - Math 2, 1971-1975 (Box 12)
    - California, Oberwolfach, Zurich, Ithaca, 1984 (Box 12)
    - Slides, 1985-1987 (Box 12)
    - Slides, 1988-1990 (Box 12)
    - Slides, 1991-1996 (Box 12)
    - Slide carousel 2-4, Undated (Box 12)
    - Slide lists for box 32, Undated (Box 32)
    - Vienna, Israel, California, Japan, Oslo, Ithaca, 1976-1980 (Box 32)
    - Israel, Britain, Switzerland, Berlin, France, 1978-1980 (Box 32)
    - Ithaca, Israel, DC, Germany, Brazil, Argentina, 1980-1982 (Box 32)
    - Germany, Ithaca, Israel, New Orleans, 1982-1983 (Box 32)
    - New Orleans, Ithaca, Rocky Mountain, 1983 (Box 32)
    - Spain, France, 1983 (Box 32)
    - UK, Ithaca, Minnesota, Undated (Box 32)
    - Moscow, unlabelled slides, Undated (Box 32)
    - Negatives (in three boxes), 1947-1971 (Box 23)
- Series X. Digital files
  - Digital files relating to his mathematics oral history project and other aspects of his career